calendarlabs.com 2019-03-12

# CalendarLabs Privacy Policy

At calendarlabs.com, we process some personal data. Below is a description of what, how, and why we gather and store user data.   
For all users who visit our website, we store: 

Web server log: IP address, pages visited by that IP address, link clicked to get here, browser name and version, and time stamp Third parties collect similar information; see “Third-Party Privacy Policies” below For all users who actively make changes to site settings, we store: 

Setting preferences, which are not personally identifiable, i.e., the cookies are stored in the browser and not on our servers. These settings include: Calendar settings, Preferred units, Cities in your World Clock, “Home” location   
For users who sign in to their personal user account, we also store: 

\- Your email address (will not be sold nor distributed to any third party unrelated to calendarlabs.com)   
\- Your password (hashed)   
\- Your chosen username, if any   
\- List of log-ins   
\- Log of changes you made to your account   
\- Events added in PDF calendar lists   
For newsletter subscribers, we store:   
Email address, IP address, and time of sign-up, Newsletters received and opened, Additional parameters may be stored by MailChimp, who we use to send our newsletter; see “Third-Party Privacy Policies” below For paying supporters and subscribers. 

IP Address and Cookies   
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our websites. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. 

Short-lived cookies die when you close the browser. Most long-lived cookies are stored for 10 years (1 year in the EU), to ensure your settings are not lost even if you visit the site infrequently, e.g., such as printing a calendar once a year. All cookies are stored in your browser, so your settings are lost when the cookies are deleted. 

Sensitive Information   
We have security measures in place. We will never ask for sensitive information. In the GDPR, “sensitive information” is defined as: “personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, and the processing of genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation.” We recommend you do not add such information to our services, such as calendars, countdowns, or any other calendarlabs.com application. 

External Links   
This site contains links to other sites. calendarlabs.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the linked websites. 

We use SurveyMonkey for online surveys. We may ask for your contact information, such as your email address. This information is used to contact you if necessary. 

Advertising   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit calendarlabs.com. These companies may use aggregated information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information about this practice and your possibility to opt out, click here. 

Third-Party Privacy Policies   
We facilitate logging in and sharing via social media accounts   
We use Braintree and Paypal for supporters and subscribers   
We use MailChimp to distribute our Newsletter   
Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website and/or other websites   
Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other websites   
Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting YourAdChoices or on our new privacy settings page, which will become avaiable by My 25, 2018 

Third parties we use for advertising:   
\- [Exponential](http://exponential.com/privacy/)   
Subject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collects and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time. For more details including access requests and complaints, review their [privacy policy](http://exponential.com/privacy/) or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.com Exponential uses ANON_ID (persistent tracking cookie), by domain tribalfusion.com. The anonymous hashed id in the cookie links the web user's browser to a profile which contains the behaviours the user has displayed. This is stored for 3 months.   
\- [Google DFP/AdX](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

We may use other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies to serve ads. They may also use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

Third parties we use for logging in:   
\- [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)   
\- [Google](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=no)   
\- [Microsoft](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-US/privacystatement)   
\- [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy)   
\- [Amazon](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=footer_privacy?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)
